

Ankit Tiwari

Web Developer

Motivated IT Professional filled with the enthusiasm to create new ideas. Over 3 years of experience as a web developer specializing in website and mobile application development. Worked on a variety of projects, including front and back end development.

- ankittiwari665@gmail.com
- +91 7836048635
- Naya bans gali no-2 Noida sector-15

Education

- Master of Computer Applications in (2014-2017) with 69% From V.B.S.P University Jaunpur (U.P)
- 12th in 2009 with 69% From U.P Board
- 10th in 2007 with 65% From U.P Board

Skills

PHP

Codeigniter

Laravel

HTM/CSS

Jquery

Bootstrap

Language

Hindi

English

Work Experience

 Webnotics Solution Pvt.Ltd (Nov 2020 to Present)

To Write Server Side Web Application login for codeigniter & laravel alog with web service mobile app.

Work On Following Projects: Jobswiper, weineunderland

Tecorb Technologies

(june 2018 to oct 2020)

To Write Server Side Web Application login for codeigniter & laravel alog with web service mobile app.

Work On Following Projects:

Goblujay, maplebears outhasia, intellepark, fours quareoutdoor

Hobbies

Travel | Listening Music